♪ In the not too
distant future ♪
♪ Next Sunday AD
♪ There was a guy named Joel
♪ Not too different
from you or me ♪
♪ He worked at
Gizmonic Institute ♪
♪ Just another face
in a red jumpsuit ♪
♪ He did a good job
cleaning up the place ♪
♪ But his bosses
didn't like him ♪
♪ So they shot him into space
♪ We'll send him cheesy movies
♪ The worst we can find
♪ La la la
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ And we'll monitor his mind
♪ La la la
♪ Now keep in mind,
♪ Joel can't control where
the movies begin or end ♪
♪ La la la
♪ Because he used
those special parts ♪
♪ To make his robot friends
♪ Robot roll
Let's go.
♪ Cambot
♪ Gypsy
Hi girl.
♪ Tom Servo
What a cool guy.
♪ Crow
Wise cracker
♪ If you're wondering how
he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science facts
♪ La la la
♪ Then repeat to yourself
♪ It's just a show
♪ I should really just relax
♪ For Mystery Science
Theater 3000 ♪
(doors whirring)
(mechanical scatting)
- Oh, hi everybody.
Welcome to the
Satellite of Love.
I've asked Joel if
he'd raise the level
on the sarcasm sequencer.
- That ought to do
it, right there.
- Oh yes, oh while you're at it,
why don't you keep
digging into my back?
A warm, relaxing massage
with a screwdriver?
Oh, sign me up for that.
- I think it's working.
- The great Crow speaks?
Oh.
Let me anoint your
beak with scented oils.
Membership in the Crow fan club?
Oh it's a dream
come true for me.
- [Magic Voice] Commercial
sign in 15 seconds.
- Commercials?
Oh boy, I can't wait.
30 second materialistic
soundbites
that insult our intelligence?
Oh, give me more of those.
- I'm gonna have to adjust
Tom's sarcasm sequencer.
We'll be back after that.
- Commercial sign in 5,
- Is the great Joel Robinson
going to honor me
- 4, 3, 2.
with his attention?
A blessing in disguise?
- Commercial sign on.
- I don't think so.
Oh dig a little harder, Joel.
I can't feel the pain yet.
(upbeat music)
- I think you got him
set on constant sarcasm
and you're gonna want to have
him on random, pretty much.
I think.
- Uh duh, no kidding.
Yeah, I put him
on random sarcasm,
so he'll only be sarcastic
at the appropriate time,
like when someone
mentions like Pia Zadora.
- Actually, I think
making fun of her
has become a cliche.
Everybody does it
and you know, in her favor,
she was in a John
Water's film, you guys.
- Okay, well what
about Dan Quayle?
- Oh look, Dan Quayle scares
me as much as the next guy
but everybody and their sister
has come up with
sarcastic Dan Quayle quip.
It's just too easy.
- I'm not even gonna
mention Gallagher then.
- Oh, he is my absolute
all time favorite.
Oh paying money to have
watermelon sprayed all over you.
Oh give me more of that.
Oversized props mixed
with undersized talent.
Oh put me in the front row.
Excuse me, mister shopkeeper,
can I trade in my volume
of Annotated Shakespeare
for a tape of melon crazy?
Oh please, may I, oh.
- Oh, take it easy,
the elusive uber lords
are calling here.
- Look, I run the
operation around here
and I say you do the
invention exchange first.
- Geeze, I don't mind
as long as you guys
aren't planning on stealing
another one of my ideas.
- That's good, get
everything he says down
and then make a sketch
of what he's just done.
What, what?
Didn't I tell you to do the
invention exchange, first?
- Well, all right.
My invention this week
is about a junk drawer.
Every home should
have a junk drawer
and a lot of people don't
know how you get 'em started.
So, I invented this is
which is junk drawer helper.
It comes in a little bag
and it's got a
few of those items
that are great for
starting a junk drawer.
Pretty soon you accumulate a
whole drawer full of stuff.
Anyway, there's stuff like
a C02 cartridge in there,
a plastic golf ball.
A card to a Harley
Davidson dealership.
- That's mine.
- Silly putty
and a little flower, okay,
and before you know it.
It's filled with junk, see.
- Hey.
- That's how you get started.
What do you think?
- Well, actually we've
got a really cool
invention this week.
I just hope we can find it
through all this junk in here.
- Yeah, you're not the only
with a junk drawer, you know?
- Yeah, wow, look at all this.
Oh you remember this?
Remember this, the plastic butt
from when we were selling
the thruster busters?
- Very important for
your training, Frank.
Oh, and look, world's
greatest grandmother.
Norman Bates gave me that.
- Oh, that is so sweet.
Oh, by the way, doctor,
I forgot to tell the
product placement people
called me today, I told them,
in no uncertain terms,
we never ever ever
do product placements.
- That's good to
remember, Frank.
You're learning.
- Okay, thanks a lot.
Yeah, I'm trying to learn.
- Oh and Frank, when you put
the tray back in the drawer,
please refill it with water.
- Oh okay, I'm sorry.
I'll try to remember that.
Oh wait, I'm gonna do, quick,
some quick impressions for you
and for you guys up there,
Sally Field on a bowling team.
My league likes me, they
really really like me.
Thank you, very much.
Oh, another quick
impression for you.
The drummer from Def Leppard,
ladies and gentlemen.
Thank you very much.
Oh another quick one, a
real quick one for you.
Charles Lindbergh,
ladies and gentlemen.
Charles Lindbergh.
- Frank, we don't have time
for that kind of nonsense now.
We've got to find the
invention in here.
- Okay, what's.
- What's this stuck this
to the bottom of the...
Hey, it's Abe Vigoda
from Barney Miller.
- TV's Fish.
- Bernice, I'm telling you
I haven't had a
good BM in weeks.
- Joel, your
experiment this week
is called First
Spaceship to Venus.
It stars an international cast
that will leave you
bilingually tortured.
Well, bon appetite, mon ami.
(alarm blaring)
(all shouting)
- Oh, movie sign.
Oh, like I'm supposed
to be afraid.
(doors whirring)
Oh, a good movie this time?
I don't think so.
Oh look, it's in total
annihilation vision.
- [Joel] You know,
it's Totalvision.
It used to be in 80% vision.
- Ah, NASA's third birthday.
- It's Estes Park Colorado
and that's the Mars
Snooper up there.
- [Servo] Oh, let's go home.
Oh.
(tense music)
- I've looked at clouds
from both sides now.
- [Servo] A sneeze.
Billions and billions
of snot particles.
- [All] First.
Spaceship.
On.
Venus.
- [Joel] Oh that's nice.
- [All] Hey, where you going?
Come back here.
- [Joel] Oh at least
this will be different.
- Yoko.
- Hey, wait, wait.
Come on.
- Come back.
- Yoko.
- Grab this one.
- [Servo] Grab it, see if it.
- [Joel] Nothing.
Oh, he'll stay, Gordon.
- [Servo] Gordon, Gordon.
Joseph, come on.
Oh.
- [Crow] What a
tease, a title tease.
- [Joel] I hate it.
- Hugh, there goes Hugo.
- [Joel] I'm gonna
miss those titles.
- Yeah.
(dramatic music)
- [Narrator] In 1900 and 85,
during the course of
the work undertaken
to irrigate the Gobi Desert.
- [Joel] The goofy desert?
- [Narrator] Fragment
of rock was discovered.
Several remarkable
features of this rock
attracted the attention
of the scientists
engaged on the project.
- [Joel] Stinky cheese, ugh.
- [Narrator] Contained a spool.
- A spool sample, if you will.
- [Narrator] Further
analysis showed the material
to be extraterrestrial
in origin.
- [Servo] Extra meat.
- [Narrator] And not
of human manufacture.
- And it had never been
loved by it's mother.
- [Narrator] Where
did it come from?
- [Joel] Oh, that's how they
make wonder roast chicken.
- [Narrator] Then
somebody remembered
that in June 1900
and 80 in Siberia.
- Somebody?
- [Servo] Thank goodness
they remembered.
- [Narrator] Equivalent in force
to a hydrogen bomb.
An explosion visible
within a radius
of 350 miles.
At the time, it was
thought to have been caused
by a giant meteor.
77 years later.
- [Joel] Ah, who knew?
- Go figure.
- Phooey.
- [Narrator] Point of impact
and to find some debris
of what was called
the Tan Gu Meteor.
- Tongue goo meteor sandwich.
- [Narrator] Shortly
afterwards, under the auspices
of the World Federation
for Space Research,
scientists meet to
celebrate the anniversary
of the establishment
- Can I borrow a pencil?
- [Narrator] of the first
space station on the moon.
- [Servo] I can't miss.
I can't read the
board from here.
- [Narrator] Professor
Hemingway from the United States
makes a public statement
about the famous meteor.
- [Joel] Ah, got it.
- I hate it.
It's famous, it's a meteor.
Thank you.
- Are calculations indicate,
confirmed also by the
results recently transmitted
to us by our colleagues
on Luna Three
that the mysterious Tonga meteor
was really a spaceship.
- Talks like
a Jerry Anderson puppet.
- From another planet.
Which exploded in the
air before landing.
- [Joel] So, I was
wondering if you wanted
to go have dinner
maybe a little bit on,
later on, you know?
Could really get it on.
(overlapping talking)
- [Narrator] Reporters
all over the nation
are waiting to hear what
the nuclear physicist,
Professor Orloff, has to say.
- [Joel] Back off, pal.
Orloff's here, he's a real man.
- Professor Orloff,
is this another hoax
of the flying saucer variety?
- And what about this spool
that was found in a desert
some 350 miles from the
crater of the explosion?
- [Servo] What do you
think about Roseann
singing the national anthem?
- I believe there was
a grave emergency.
When the rockets normally
used for deceleration
refused to function,
the captain of the spaceship
decided to save
what he considered
was most valuable.
I'm referring,
naturally, to this spool,
which may contain a
document of prime importance
in an unknown language.
Recorded, apparently,
by a magnetic process.
- Naturally.
(tense music)
- [Joel] Hey, it's
Vanilla Ice's grandfather.
- [Narrator] Expert
linguists was offered access
to the world's largest computer,
who tried to decipher
this strange language.
(ethereal whirring)
- Dear diary, today
I became a diary.
- [Narrator] This
is Doctor Chen Yu.
- [Joel] Gesundheit.
- [Narrator] Not only is he one
of the world's leading
authorities on languages
but also his biological work
is of immense importance.
Humanity is in debt to him
for the technique
of transforming
inorganic substances
into foodstuffs.
- Look, he's got
his trainee hat on.
- [Narrator] He
directs the committee
with world famous mathematician,
Professor Sikarna,
who's work rivals
even that of Einstein.
- Morty Einstein.
- In the astrophysical domain,
we've made rapid progress
and although we
haven't deciphered
the mysterious message,
we have determined the
ships launching base.
At the moment, there
can be no doubt.
This spaceship.
- [Servo] Is goofy.
- Was launched within
our solar system.
I can even say that it
was definitely launched
from within the
path of our planet.
- [Joel] Then why don't you?
- Since there can be
no life on Mercury,
there is only one other planet
that it could of come from.
- Uranus.
(all goofy laughing)
- Sister planet, Venus,
the morning star.
(tense music)
- [Servo] Look, it's
the most advanced
slurppy machine ever built.
There's the dub master.
- [Joel] Would you like some
curly fries with your gyro?
- Listen.
- [Joel] Isn't that grand?
(ethereal whirring)
Beautiful.
- I love this part.
- [Servo] I can't understand it.
Could you turn the bass
down a little bit, please?
(indistinct alien language)
- Do that again.
- The elements
existing on Earth.
- That's right.
It certainly is.
A chemical, physical
analysis of the atmosphere--
- Professor.
- [Joel] Don't interrupt me.
(ethereal whirring)
- [Servo] I thought
this thing had Dolby.
- Oh, this is what the teens
are listening to today.
- [Joel] It's neat.
- [Servo] That proves
we were dressed
too casually for this.
- What we have just heard
are the first words
of the inhabitants
of another planet.
A cosmic document.
- [Joel] You're high.
- [Servo] Oh that's nice.
Well, lunch everybody?
- Yes, but it's unfortunate
that the magnetic spool
was damaged through the
effect of the high temperature
which prevailed aboard
the cosmic vessel
at the time of the crash
and that's the reason
we've only heard
a part of the text.
We must try to find a
method to renovate the rest.
- [Servo] It's Maru.
- First, we'll immerse the spool
in a chemical
catalytically medium
and after that, subject
it to radiation.
Chen Yu?
- [All] Gesundheit.
- Yes, that's a very good idea.
All that we have learned
indicates that on Venus
there is a highly
developed life form.
Yet, I'm wondering why
Venus stays silent.
It's very surprising.
- They have trailer parks there.
- Now, we know a little
of this language,
we must, at every cost,
communicate with them.
- I agree with you.
It's high time...
- Ah, quit kissing up.
(overlapping talking)
- Well, then I'd like
propose a course of action.
Now, I think the most
logical thing to do
would be to request
that our governments
consent to train all the
radio and radar stations
of the world on Venus.
(electronic beeping)
- [Servo] Well, good morning.
It's 8:15 and time
for our crazy call.
We're gonna call Venus
and pretend we're Pluto.
Uh, so that's cheese tortellini
and a couple of
shrimp croissant.
(phone ringing)
- This is apartment 12 B.
Could you send up some heat?
- Polar station calling
moon space station.
Attention, please.
Luna Three.
Attention please, Luna Three.
- [Joel] Uh, quit playing Pong.
There's a message coming in.
- Thank you.
- This is statin Luna Three.
- Mr. Matt Mason here.
We're bendy and flexible.
- Calling Earth.
No replies yet from Venus.
Our signals are
reaching the planet
but so far those no reply.
We'll keep you informed.
- [Joel] Hugs and kisses, bunny.
- Look out for the box spring!
- [Servo] Watch your head.
(mock shouting)
- [All] We are scientists.
Get out of our way.
- Good morning, my friends.
- May I please
have an interview?
- This afternoon, I have news...
- [Servo] Watch it, watch it.
It's coming around again.
- Hey, it's coming around.
- As you probably know already.
- [Servo] Somebody's
gonna get canned.
- Is now completed
and ready to set forth
on our exploration of space.
- [Servo] Here it comes again.
- Look out.
- [Servo] Guys,
excuse me, watch it.
- Hey, guys get back.
- Look out, here it comes.
- Of the Cosmostraiter.
Instead of sending her to Mars,
she will be directed
toward the planet Venus.
- Venus.
V-E-N.
- Have you any idea of
the date of the takeoff?
- One more question, if
you don't mind, Professor.
- Do you think there's
anybody living on Venus?
- Did you manage to...
- [Joel] Boy, jump cut to the.
- No, my friends,
Venus is silent
but we'll soon discover why.
- And who's going with you?
- Here it comes.
Watch your backs,
watch your backs.
- Some of the other scientists
will take part in
this expedition.
They are all first
class specialists.
- And snappy dressers.
- From the among
the most qualified
in their particular fields.
- [Servo] Well over
four feet tall.
- They, with others
who are coming,
will form the crew
of Cosmostraiter one.
(upbeat music)
(Servo coughing)
- Well, all the
units of propulsion
are in perfect working order.
- [Crow] Thanks, Lenin.
- The crew can now attend
to their personal affairs.
We'll start late tomorrow night.
We'll fly flowing the
hyperbolic trajectory.
- Good, I'll make a last change.
- See you later.
- [Servo] He's
wearing a t-shirt.
- Will you please
make a thorough...
- [Joel] He's Mr. T.
- Right away, professor.
- This is intervision
calling the world.
- Hi, this is the world.
I'm not in right now but if--
- For the
Cosmostraiter's rockets.
- Nevermind.
- Out rising now is Brinkmann.
The first American spaceman
to land on the moon.
- [Servo] Oh, I don't think so.
Run.
- Run.
- Ladies and gentlemen,
I have an important
announcement to make.
- [Joel] I'll bet.
- Intervision is
going to present you
minute by minute, the
historic launching
of the Cosmostraiter.
We know very well how much
you'd like to be here with us.
- Oh yeah.
- Unfortunately,
that's impossible.
The only ones admitted
are those directly
concerned with the countdown
and final blast
off of the rocket.
So, I will try to
describe in detail
everything that's taking place.
- [Joel] Or use a camera.
- Intervision will bring
to you the wonderful story
of this great event.
Ah, but here come the
first members of the crew.
- [Joel] 2 Live Crew.
- Among them is Professor
Durand, the chief engineer.
He's a french scientist,
well known for his work...
- I'll sign it lots
of love, Dr. Durand.
- We'll load the cronocopter
later on in the evening.
That's of course if
it's all right with you.
- Yes, of course.
- I've checked out your
electronic equipment.
- Good.
- [Joel] Thanks, Eb.
- Professor Durand, report
from station A, here.
Celestial charts are ready.
- Thank you.
- [Servo] Bunk
number four is ready.
Go ahead, number 50.
- Hello, Durand.
- Oh, Durand.
I'm glad to see you again.
- So am I.
- Still working as hard?
- How 'bout showing me
your latest creation
in robots?
- How 'bout you shutting up
and letting me get in
a word in edge wise?
- The pieces.
- Omigow.
Come here, Omigow.
- [Servo] What's that say?
- [Joel] Bidi-bidi-bidi-bidi.
Yes, Ms. Benny.
- Oh cute.
Hey, you missed a spot.
(whimsical music)
- [Joel] So whimsical.
- Omigow, what's
the weather report
for the next 10 hours?
- [Servo] Well, it's gonna
be 50 degrees and cloudy.
- [Robot] The
round tip will rise
four (mumbling).
- [Servo] What?
- [Robot] Four (mumbling).
- [Joel] Full Billy bao?
What?
- Why, that's fantastic.
- [Servo] It's babble.
- Your latest invention?
- Oh, nothing special.
- You can say that again.
- Just a small gadget.
- You're a lot too
modest, Durand.
What else does it do?
- [Servo] Oh, I don't think so.
- He reacts to stimuli
in his environment
and evaluates them with
his electronic brain.
- [Joel] That means
you can kick him.
- Managed to give Omigow
an elementary memory.
- What a stupid robot.
- Perhaps he might be consent
to play chess with me.
- Why of course.
Why shouldn't he?
- Hello, all.
- Oh, Harringway.
- [Servo] How much
does a herring weigh?
- [Joel] About a pound.
- Have reached Urania.
Eight of them, scientists,
mathematicians,
and astrophysicists.
Seven men and a woman.
- [Joel] And a little lady.
- The physician
of the expedition
and has already spent
two years on Luna Three.
- Sumiko.
- I will as soon as
my lawyer get here.
- Brinkmann.
Have I changed that much?
- [Joel] Yeah, you used
to be a Swedish man.
- I don't know.
I've got it.
You hair used to hang
down to your waist.
- Mr. Brinkmann.
- Yes?
- You forgot this.
- Oh, thank you.
- [Joel] Your M, sir.
- You think that's funny?
- Robert Brinkmann,
the man who's always
forgetting something.
- I have a reputation for that.
You're right.
But there are things
I'll never forget.
- [Joel] Right
Sarah, I mean Jan.
What was your name again?
- No, Brinkmann.
On a voyage of this kind,
there'll be no room
for excess baggage.
- [Servo] Emotional baggage?
- 30 hours left.
30 hours and the
Cosmostraiter will blast off
into the unknown.
- [Joel] Kinda grabs you
by the popo, don't it?
- Now we will leave the air.
In the next few hours,
the crew of eight
picked for the Cosmostraiter
will be unable to
communicate with the world.
They're going into a state
of artificially induced sleep
till the time comes
for them to take off.
This is to make sure that they
will be in good
physical condition for
the effort to come.
This is intervision.
Good afternoon.
- Sure is.
- Just try to forget me.
(tense music)
- [Joel] Mommy?
Can I have a glass of water?
- Brinkmann, in two
minutes you'll be asleep
like all your kind,
whether you want to or not.
- [Servo] Oh I
want to, I want to.
- Now, I'm gonna have
you watch this movie
called Mannequin, is
stars Andrew McCarthy.
- We'll be able to see
and hear your heart.
- [Joel] Psychedelic.
(tense music)
- I'm very glad you're
coming with us, Sumiko.
- [Servo] What did you call me?
- That way, I'll be near you.
- Your heart beat is normal.
- Oh, tell her you love
her, ya big galoot.
- My heart is--
- No, Brinkmann, no.
No, please, we mustn't
speak of that, ever.
- Let's talk about
your pancreas.
- [Joel] Okay.
(mock snoring)
(somber music)
- Goodnight, Robert.
- [Servo] Goodnight!
Oh, sorry.
- It's time for you to
sleep, too, Dr. Sumiko.
- Yes, you're right.
(somber music)
- [Joel] Horny,
heiny, honey, heeny.
- [Servo] Killed it again.
(somber music)
- [Joel] Oh, she's gonna
be watching My Demon Lover
to put her to sleep.
I see.
(mock snoring)
- [Woman Voiceover]
This is Intervision.
Intervision calling the world.
- [Servo] Call your cable
company for Intervision.
- [Woman Voiceover]
Until the blastoff.
Tension is mounting
among the scientists
and technicians on the base
and zero hour approaches.
- [Crow] It's always zero hour
with these goons around.
- [Woman Voiceover]
Everything is ready.
All we're waiting
for is the crew
and here they are.
- Motley Crue.
- News of the crew are finished.
They are now
boarding the vehicles
which will take them to the...
- [Servo] The whole
alphabet is there.
They're going to
spell out the words,
goodbye suckers.
- [All] M-I-C.
- [Joel] See you real soon.
- [All] K-E-Y.
- [Joel] Why?
Because we're an
international task force.
- Goodbye.
Write if you get word.
Bring your duct tape
back for our outfits.
- [Joel] You're all
invited back next week
to this locality
to have a helping
of our hospitality.
- 51.
52.
53.
- Hey, it's the
honeycomb hideout.
- 54.
55.
- Kinda.
- 56.
57.
- [Servo] This is the day
the teddy bears fly to Venus.
- 59.
60.
- [Joel] I can count to 60.
- Rockets primed,
ready for blast off.
- [Servo] Yeah.
- Breathe calmly.
Relax.
- [Servo] Sit a spell,
take your shoes off.
- Don't tense up.
- Ignition system ready.
- 10 seconds.
Nine, eight.
- [Servo] Seven.
- Seven.
- Six.
- [Crow] He said six twice.
- [Joel] Yeah, I've done this.
- Four.
- Standby.
- Three.
- Hey, it's HAL.
- Two.
- I'm sorry, Dave.
- One.
Zero.
- [Servo] Whoa.
- Hey, it's a Jack
Nicholson party.
- [Joel] Light
blooming ground flower
than get away.
- [Servo] Oh we
got to split, guys.
Let's get out of here.
- [Joel] Oh, here we go..
- [Servo] We got something
neat to show ya, Joel.
- Yeah.
- Okay, cool.
(doors whirring)
- Okay, I think it's all done.
- Yeah, it's great.
- I'm gonna go get Joel.
- All right, I'll wait here.
This is getting, it's so cool.
- It's the neatest
thing in the world.
Come on.
That's it, keep
your eyes closed.
Keep 'em closed.
- Okay, don't look.
Don't look, you promise?
- Okay, all right.
- It's a super surprise
with cream on top.
You ready?
Open your eyes.
- Yeah.
- Ta-DA.
- Oh, a surprise.
Do you want me to open it?
- It's open already,
you silly willy.
- Oh, what was it?
- Servo.
- It's the XT-5000
Ramchip super configured
limited edition
lightning interface.
Model L.
- Wow.
Well does it talk?
- Well, Joel, it's the only
coolest robot in the world.
It's our entry into
the land of robotics.
- Oh, yeah, it is really cool.
It's got this
thing-a-ma-jig here
and this kind of head thing.
- Yeah, that's the powered light
XL 4-40 adapter plate.
I made that.
- I soldered it.
- Wow, so could I
ask it a question?
- Well, sure.
- Sure, if it'll
make you feel better.
- Yeah, um.
Wow, he's probably so powerful,
I could probably ask it just
about anything, pretty much.
- Yeah, pretty much.
- Okay, uh.
I actually, I got
a question here.
That I got.
Okay, XT-4000.
- 5000.
- I mean, XT 5000.
What integer can be
the sum of itself
and a number less than the
positive square root of 30?
- Here we go.
- Here comes the answer.
- Cool, huh?
- Wow.
Is it supposed to do that?
- Yeah, that's the way
the XT communicates.
He talks in foam.
- Oh, well that's kind of an
interesting way to interface.
Kind of a bubble memory, huh?
- Yeah, thank you.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
- Here comes the answer.
- Let me check it out here.
- What's it say, Crow?
- I haven't quite figured
out how to read it yet.
- You guys, it's kinda messy.
- Oh, well I guess are
computers are bug proof, huh?
Well I'd like to be
on the mailing list
for one of those.
Sign me up.
Well, its starting
to pile up here.
- Yeah.
So.
We thought you'd
be happy for us.
- No, it's.
- Can you see if it's
commercial sign yet, Crow?
- I think we got
commercial sign, you guys.
Yeah, it's really neat.
(upbeat music)
- [Servo] Sorry about
the mess there, Joel.
- [Joel] That's okay.
- We'll clean it up later.
- [Joel] All right.
(tense music)
- Unit three, calling Urania.
Have Cosmostraiter
on our radar screen.
Appearance normal.
- Well, feeling all right?
- [Joel] Not feeling
too good ourselves.
- Right in the clouds.
- I'll be fine as soon
as I scrape my butt
off the ceiling.
- Someway behind us.
- I'm gonna loosen this belt.
It's uncomfortable.
(mock grunting)
- Hey, be careful, don't forget.
There's no gravity.
We're in free fall now.
- [Joel] No gravity?
(mock laughter)
- I love to laugh.
Long and loud and clear.
(goofy laughter)
- [Joel] Oh, even I
gotta laugh at that.
- Nice trust, buddy.
(all laughing)
- [Servo] Wendy, Michael,
John, we can fly.
- Gravity field, will you?
(laughing)
- [Joel] Oh, that's rich.
Oh.
- Be careful.
Not pushing the button.
- Hey, you're pushing 50.
You better get down here.
(all laughing)
- [Joel] Oh, let him go.
- [Servo] The
laugh meter's high.
(all laughing)
- [Joel] Oh fun.
Oh, Steve, your shin
bone is sticking out.
- That was a dirty trick.
(mock laughter)
- [Joel] Well, our first report
says there's lot of good nature
ribbing going on up there.
- This is Luna Three.
We are receiving you well.
Over and out.
- Hello, Luna Three, we
hear you loud and clear.
- [Servo] How are
we coming in, over?
- Plus five.
Course normal, course normal.
- Our course is exactly
hyperbolic, no deviations.
- We are passing within
1,200 miles of you.
- This is Luna Three.
We have established
visual contact with you.
- That's the Sinus Roris crater.
- Hope there's a
good place to park.
- On the top of
it is Luna Three.
- There's the solar reflector.
They're signaling us.
- [Servo] Oh, blue moon,
you saw me standing alone.
- Without a dream in her heart.
- [Joel] Without
a love of her own.
- That's where her husband fell.
I brought him back to the camp
but he was already dead.
- He was all busted up outside.
- We were friends.
You know, Sumiko is
a wonderful woman.
- This is Luna Three.
- [Servo] Quit clowning
around and get back to work.
- I picked up unexpected swarms
of meteorites on our radar.
Their present trajectory shows
that they may cross your path
and be very dangerous.
- We are receiving you.
- But we can only
hear your chin.
- Here are the
trajectory coordinates
and orbital philosophy.
Alpha X, seven
degrees, two minutes.
Beta Epsilon, 48 degrees.
42 minutes.
- [Servo] Now, here's
Geordie with the weather.
- Listen, I've had an
extremely urgent message
from Luna Three.
A meteorite warning.
- Says you.
- Professor Sikarna, here's
the latest meteorite report.
Alpha X, seven
degrees, two minutes.
Beta Epsilon, 48
degrees, 42 minutes.
- The meteorite swarm
should reach us in 48 hours,
at the latest.
- [Joel] Hey, wasn't
he on Mork and Mindy.
- Keep close radio
contact with Luna Three.
- And the seventh caller
will get a free album.
- Calling Luna Three.
We've received your
meteorite warning.
We'll be sending you regular
coordinates of our course...
(all mock shouting)
(soft tense music)
- This is the beginning
of my personal log book.
- [Joel] Mr. Toothbrush,
you're the only one
who really understands me.
- Of the Cosmostraiter.
The computer is keeping
us on our course.
In case of unforeseen
circumstances,
it can take immediate decisions
to alter our speed or direction.
This electronic brain
will be our pilot
for the next 30 days.
- [Servo] And our friend.
- Because no human
being could handle
the immensely complex machines
of the spaceship by himself.
- Expect Steve Allen.
- To now, we have
covered a distance
of 2,600,000 miles.
- [Servo] Your mileage may vary.
- Dr. Omigura is noting
our reactions carefully
and keeping close check on
our health and well being.
A special liquid food,
which can easily be absorbed
in a state of no gravity
is proving very
successful with all of us.
- [Joel] And she's
got a lot of fun stuff
to keep us busy, too.
- French dressing, I love it.
- Our chief engineer
spends most of his time
in his machine shop,
testing his automats
over and over again.
- [Servo] Oh come on,
that's a rock tumbler.
- It is thanks to them
and to the fact that they
are in perfect running order
that we are relieved
of many tiresome tasks.
- Like acting.
- Our expert in cybernetics
has to be everywhere.
He is one of the key
men of the expedition.
- [Joel] All right, all right.
I'll get it.
I'm coming.
- Professor Sikarna
devotes all his time
to the message from Venus.
He and T'chen Yu are trying
to decipher the damaged spool
which means they spend
long hours at the markets.
- [Servo] In little
yellow boots.
- The electronic brain
is working night and day
but no can be sure what
the result will be.
(mock shouting)
(soft tense music)
- Harringway, our commander,
is keeping a constant
check on our course.
- Well, this is the last
of the bathroom tissue.;
- Was active last night.
It switched the rockets
on for nearly 17 seconds.
- [Servo] Oh, I'm impressed.
- Perhaps to avoid
the meteor swarm.
- We won't be running
into it till tomorrow.
- Looks like your automats
don't have the same idea
that you do.
- [Servo] They make sandwiches.
- [Joel] Dear, toothbrush.
- Professor Orloff is an
enthusiastic chess player.
- [Servo] Doh.
- He has beaten all of us
but I think he's found
his master in Omigow.
- [Servo] King me.
- King G 8.
- [Servo] Line.
Line, please.
Line!
- [Robot] King E6.
(Crow laughing robotically)
- Take that, pink boy.
- It's amazing.
He plays his end
game wonderfully.
- [Joel] Boy, do I stink.
- I thought that I had got him
but you see, he's
put his king on E6
and I'm forced into
the corner at H8.
(whimsical music)
- Good evening and welcome
to Alfred Hitchcock presents.
Just uh, just that joke.
- [Joel] Good one.
- [Robot] King E7.
Checkmate, next move.
- [Servo] Oh, I'll
alert the media.
- [Joel] He's a kookster.
(goofy whimsical music)
- That is the 10th
match that I've lost.
I should give up, I guess.
- That's the spirit.
- I would suggest that you
make an improvement in Omigow.
- Oh really?
- If he only had a heart.
- A brain.
- A home.
- [Servo] Da nerve.
- Don't you think you
could be able to do that?
Just a little bit
of heart, Jerome.
- [Servo] Yes, I
think I could do that.
- Oh, he'll do anything to win.
- [Servo] The dryers off kilter.
- [Joel] Whoa, bonny's done.
- [Servo] Fries are up.
- [Joel] Irwin Allen presents.
- Chock full of nuts.
- [Servo] Guess somebody forgot
to set the parking break.
(tense music)
- Big one.
- Quick, switch on
the emergency gyro.
- [Joel] Pop-o-matic
pops the dice,
pop the six and you move twice.
Race your men around the track
and try to send the others back.
That's pop-o-matic trouble.
(tense music)
- [Servo] Somebody get that?
- I'm here, Steve.
- [Servo] Oh.
- [Joel] Hold me, Steve, again.
- Is that your leg?
- [Servo] Well, fries are done.
Get off of me.
- Brinkmann, see if T'Chen
Yu and Sikarna are all right.
- [Joel] What about us?
- [Servo] Oh.
(tense music)
- How could this happen?
- [Joel] There.
- I thought that
the Cosmostraiter
was able to avoid meteor
storms automatically.
- [Joel] Now you can play
flag football anytime.
- She didn't react
quickly enough.
She was regulated to a
shower under mass eight.
That was why we had to
switch on the emergency...
- [Servo] Yeah, yeah, whatever.
(tense music)
- Orloff, how much
course deviation?
- [Servo] What, personally?
So the four, carry the seven.
Boy, we're in debt
up to our eyeballs.
- 12 degrees, 17 minutes.
- Our speed?
- Constant.
Eight point two miles a second.
- My hair?
Fully coiffed, sir.
- I guess the main principle
swarm will be on us soon.
If we continue at maximum
speed, it will mean disaster.
(goofy tense music)
- [Joel] And stopped
that nutty horn section.
- Decelerate.
(upbeat music)
(tense music)
- Well, I can't think
of a better bunch
of people to die with.
- What do you mean the
motors aren't working?
What's the matter, Durand?
- [Joel] They're
not working, sir.
- [Servo] Come on.
Just put a penny in
the fusebox, baldy.
Come on.
- A meteor fragment has
damaged the deceleration unit.
We have to go outside
and try and repair
it right away.
- Outside, in this weather?
- How long before the
main swarm hits us?
- I can't say.
It may be on us any second now.
- Brinkmann, will you help me?
- Professor Sikarna and
T'chen Yu, are you all right.
- No bones broken.
- [Joel] You know,
I hurt my head.
- Please give me our
present deviation,
direction coordinates,
and corrected course.
- [Servo] In that order.
- Hey, a human and a salt
shaker fused into one.
That will put some
spice in his life.
(laughing)
- [Joel] Good one.
- Sorry.
- [Servo] Um, hey, I
gotta go to the bathroom.
- Just go in the suit.
- [Servo] Oh.
- And now it's time for
the $64,000 question.
- [Servo] Bye.
(alarm whooping)
- [Joel] What a time to
get the whooping cough.
- Whoa.
Hey, he's transparent now.
(Tom laughing)
Oh.
- [Joel] You know, Bob doesn't
matte very well, does he?
(tense music)
- Watch out.
Everybody fasten your belts.
- [Servo] Yeah, why don't you
stop breathing down my neck.
- No, uh uh.
- Uh uh.
- No, no, no, no.
- Stand by.
- Hey, look at him
squirm out there.
That's our Bob.
(tense music)
(alarm whooping)
- Is it safe to
start the motors yet?
- [Servo] Can somebody
shoot that turkey?
- Repair is completed.
Clear on back.
(all blubbering their lips)
- [Servo] Oh, all right.
- Cosmostraiter
calling Luna Three.
Cosmostraiter
Meteor swarm has passed.
- That ought to hold 'em.
- Everything okay on board.
(tense music)
- [Joel] Space the final...
Huh?
- [Narrator] Three
weeks have gone by
since we left the Earth.
We should reach Venus
in about 10 days.
In spite of our enormous speed,
the stars seem to
hang motionless.
- [Servo] On black
construction paper.
- [Narrator] Disturbances
caused by the planet.
Radio contact with Earth
is no longer possible.
- Hey, my boo boo is all better.
- Too much interference.
I can't hear a thing.
- Keep trying.
- [Joel] He's right, you know.
- Alpha X, 32
degrees, eight minute.
B to Y, seven degrees.
- You sunk my battleship.
- [Joel] You know, they're
backstage all of a sudden.
- What are you doing?
- It's a booger.
- I'm making a heart for Omigow.
10 consecutive defeats are
driving our friend crazy.
I want him to enjoy
his favorite game.
- [Joel] Hmm, thoughtful.
- I would you to do
something, also, for me.
It would be nice to see
you eat occasionally.
- [Joel] It's western
french, I made it myself.
- Sikarna said exactly
the same thing.
Professor.
- Well, I poisoned the doctor.
- What do you want?
Please, not now.
- [Joel] Well.
- Your health is
my responsibility
and you haven't eaten for days.
- I haven't a second to spare.
- [Joel] Not even for
creamy dill and chive?
- [Servo] How do you like
my new mood synthesizers?
(ethereal electronic tones)
- [Joel] Wow, Steve always
drinks my dressing my home.
Well, it's time to cut my hair
and get into a pantsuit.
- Sumiko.
You mustn't insist,
he's nervous.
He's having a very hard
time with that spool.
You understand?
- [Joel] Oh, that's great.
Who are you, anyway?
- Knight, E6, check.
- Does this guy have a job?
- [Servo] I don't think so.
(goofy whimsical music)
- He doesn't like that.
- [Joel] It hurts him.
- [Robot] King E8.
- [Servo] Think the ink?
- Mate.
- Congratulations.
You've won at last.
(all mock goofy laughing)
- [Joel] Oh, fun.
- Classical end play, I
think you deserve to win.
- Oh, quit kissing up.
- He plays a good game.
He's not very easy to beat.
- But I did it at last.
Man has defeated the machine.
- Ah, too much heart.
- [Servo] That's right,
maybe I care too much.
- Want to try?
- Well, why not?
- [Intercom] Will you all
come to the marrocks, please?
- [Servo] That's how it starts.
- It's a cosmic document.
- [Joel] All right.
- Hope there's no postage due.
- [Joel] Lite-Brite,
making things with light.
Out of sight.
Making things with Lite-Brite.
- Hey, it's a John Tesh song.
- They have finally deciphered
the last part of the spool.
It gives complete meaning
to the cosmic document.
- [Servo] It says
(goofy warbling).
(indistinct warbled
electronic voice)
- [Joel] Well, it
uh, it gets better.
Well, that's neat but we got
to get back to the lunch room.
- I will translate.
(all mock goofy warbling)
We will initially
subject the planet
to a very intense
bombardment of radiation.
Conquest and
occupation of the Earth
will then present no difficulty.
When the ionization...
- Oh, he's reading Dianetics.
- The final extermination
phase can start.
- This can only mean...
An Attack!
(tense music)
Against our planet.
- [Servo] With tympanies.
- An invasion by the
inhabitants of Venus.
- The cosmic document was
not intended for us to read.
It's a cold blooded
blueprint of destruction.
- Maybe we could--
- We must inform the Earth.
I'll try and make contact.
- But I--
- Wait, Cal.
- No, let him try.
- Will it do the Earth any
good to know what we know?
- The Earth is in danger,
we must warn them.
- [Joel] Well at least
we should try and go--
- No, our planet
was in peril before
they discovered the spool
and nothing happened.
- [Servo] He's right, it's--
- That's an argument.
As we haven't any idea how
the Venusian's calculate time.
- [Joel] Well at least we can--
- If the Earth knew of the
terrible danger threatening her,
unrest and even hysteria
would spread like wild fire
from pole to pole, the whole
world would be in a panic.
- [Joel] That's two poles.
- No, no Orloff.
I'm convinced you're wrong.
- [Joel] Oh just shut
him out like that, sure.
- For years and years, the
whole of the human race
faced the danger of atomic war.
- Yes.
- And they survived.
Not through ignorance
but through knowledge.
Because they knew
what the danger was.
No.
There won't be a panic.
(all mock screaming)
T'chen Yu, don't
you agree with me?
- I am sure that if we meet
the inhabitants of Venus,
we'll be able to convince
that it would be folly
to start that war.
- [Servo] Yeah, right.
- So, try to contact the Earth.
- [Joel] They're not
home, I left a message.
- I can't get through.
Too much disturbance from Venus.
Our signals are distorted.
(tense music)
The Earth won't hear us.
- I said, the Earth
won't hear us.
- [Joel] I'm filled with shame.
- Well, what do you say?
Should we turn back to Earth?
- [Servo] Oh and end
this dream vacation?
- No.
(all shouting)
- Return?
- [Servo] Oh, I don't think so.
- Never.
- [Servo] Cowardly retreat?
Oh please sign me up for that.
- Uh uh.
- [Joel] All right then,
we've got a war to fight.
- Durand, our speed.
- 31,000 miles per hour.
In three days, we reach Venus.
- Good, Teller check our course.
- [Joel] Yes, it's
good, isn't it?
- Orloff.
- Yes, that will be good.
- [Servo] Let's roll, guys.
- [Joel] Oh, we better
get out of here.
- Radiation is
reaching steadily.
I'll recheck.
- Mr. Crusher, take
us out of warp.
(upbeat music)
Hello and welcome to
the Satellite of Love.
I'm Crow.
- And I'm Tom Servo
and we're hosts
of the all new Match Game 78.
So let's meet our
guest, Brad Summers.
(cheering)
- Hey.
- Whoa.
- Oh, yipes.
Looks like a foreign ship
coming into our air space.
Cambot, give me rocket
number nine, quick.
Oh uh, looks like
we got company.
- Well, I'm gonna go get Joel.
- Good idea.
- Oh.
Look out, hold
me, Crow, hold me.
- What?
Hang on.
Gypsy, Gypsy girl,
whatever you do,
don't turn around.
Just don't turn around.
- Okay.
- No, no, no.
- Oh no.
Oh great, just great.
We lost Gypsy.
Where's Joel, he'd
know what to do.
Help me, you gregarious
galvanized garbage can.
Oh, the pain, the pain.
- Danger.
Danger Crow T. Robot, danger.
No, no, come on Crow,
you got me doing it now.
Get a grip, boy.
We have to remain rational.
This is just one of the
many sordid alien visitors
that fly by, exchange
dialog with us
for roughly two and a half
minutes and then leaves.
It's no big deal.
(grunting)
Oh, oh.
I do believe in spooks,
I do believe in.
Oh mommy, mommy.
- Just stop it, Tom.
Come on, get ahold of yourself.
It's a common gorilla.
Probably one of those
horrible animal experiments
they used to shoot into space.
Just a big, old dumb gorilla.
The key with these creatures
is to talk nice to 'em.
Animals can sense fear
and rip your arms
out of your sockets
and show 'em to you
in a moment's notice.
Watch this.
- Okay.
- Hey, boy.
Here, kitty kitty.
Hey, Coco.
How's it going, boy?
- Hey, he's going for it, Crow.
- Yeah.
- Wow.
- That's it, just relax.
You big dumb dolt.
Still bummed out
that humans evolved
to be a higher species?
Yeah, you idiot.
That's right.
Still dumber than a bag
full of hammers, aren't you?
Yeah.
Now, listen Tom.
- Okay.
- I know you're scared
out of your wits
but I need you to sign
that gorilla a song.
What's that song you sang
last Wednesday at Vespers?
- Oh sweet mother of mine.
But I don't understand
how that's gonna--
- Yeah, no buts, Tom.
Just start singing, boy.
- Okay.
Oh, nice gorilla.
Oh nice boy, you crummy
monkey with matted awful--
- Hey, Tom, watch it.
♪ Oh sweet mother of mine
♪ Tis only for you I pine
♪ I'll try to get bail
♪ And I'll drive up to jail
♪ And I'll spring
♪ That sweet mother of mine
- You sang that at Vespers?
- What in the world
is going on here?
- Oh Joel, there was a
gorilla at the screen.
He was looking at us
and he made us sad.
- Just take it, take it easy.
Take it easy, you guys.
Take a breath, come
on, take a breath.
We got movie sign!
(crying and shouting)
- [Servo] He was big and sweaty.
- [Joel] A gorilla in space?
I don't know.
- [Servo] It was really there.
- We really saw one.
It looked like Gino Vannelli.
- [Servo] It was terrible.
- All our efforts to
communicate with the Earth
via Luna Three have
been unsuccessful.
- [Joel] I love you,
goofy toothbrush.
- We started to accelerate
by means of rocket motors.
Professor Harringway
is guiding the ship
into an elliptical
orbit around Venus.
We are now a satellite
of this silent planet.
- [Servo] Tell me
something we don't know.
- Are still trying, but in vain,
to establish radio contact
with her inhabitants.
A thick wall of clouds
surrounds the planet.
- [Servo] Good morning.
- 3,500 miles.
- [Joel] Thank you, Sulu.
- First analysis,
Venus atmosphere.
27% carbon dioxide,
14% formaldehyde.
- The air, the
air is everywhere.
- No oxygen,
atmosphere poisonous.
- We're faced with a
difficult decision.
As you know, we can only
land and take off once.
No point in taking any
unnecessary chances.
So one of us has got
to go ahead as scout.
- 2,000 miles.
- We're close enough now.
I'll go in the crawl-o-copter.
- Oh, the crawl-o-copter.
That's your answer
for everything.
- You have got to try and
find a landing place for us.
We'll stay in orbit at 150
miles altitude, all right?
- The crawl-o-copter's ready.
- [Servo] Oh everything's
better in the crawl-o-copter.
(dramatic music)
- What, what?
Hey, hey cut it out.
You're making me cry.
- Well.
- Now, let's don't be formal.
- [Servo] Not you, too.
- Action stations.
Action stations everyone.
- [Joel] Action stations
figures sold separately.
By Miko.
- Don't do that.
- Stand by.
We are now entering the
atmosphere of Venus.
Attention.
- [Servo] Oh, a hostile planet.
Oh put me on the guest list.
- [Joel] I'm in the
Willy Wonka mobile, sir.
- [Servo] I made this from
a soft serve yogurt machine.
I call the fentoozler.
- [Joel] Well if
that don't beat all.
I'll tell you.
- [Intercom] 300 miles altitude.
- [Servo] Fly's open.
- [Intercom] Four point
three miles a second.
- Are you ready, Brinkmann?
(laughing)
- Oh the guys lunch meat.
Hi, Bill.
He's got no idea what
I'm saying to him.
You look good.
He's dead.
Good luck.
He'll never see
his family again.
Way to go, sport.
He'll be vaporized
within the hour.
We're with you.
Sucker.
- [Joel] This
baby's really comfy.
I wonder if the radio works.
- Brinkmann, hello.
Hello, Brinkmann.
- [Brinkmann] Hello?
- What's the matter
with his receiver?
- [Brinkmann] I'm
not getting you.
- [Servo] I'm getting
the ha channel.
- There's something
wrong with your receiver.
Can you hear me now?
- [Brinkmann] I
can't understand you.
Somethings wrong with
your transmitter.
- My transmitter?
Look, dick weed.
- What's the matter
with our transmitter.
- Heavy electrical disturbance.
We're completely blocked out.
- Hello, Brinkmann.
What is it, Brinkmann?
- [Joel] I knew I shouldn't
have switched from AT&T.
- Hey, I'm flying
through some confetti.
Apparently, they're throwing
me a surprise party.
(cheering)
- Radar indicates
that the surface
is extremely mountainous.
I can't see anything.
I'm completely surrounded
by thick clouds.
- [Joel] Mostly
produced by my own body.
- I can see land.
I can see land.
- [Servo] Traffic is
heavy over I-94 outbound.
- Hello, hello.
- [Servo] Hello.
- Cosmostraiter,
I can't hear you.
I'm landing...
- And I can't get up.
(ethereal ringing)
- Brinkmann is not receiving us.
I can't make contact.
- [Joel] So that's a bad thing?
- [Servo] At least we have
our Ewok suits to cheer us up.
- 2,400 feet.
- [Servo] The papers want to
know who's shirt you wear.
- Hey, he's landed on a witch.
- [Joel] We secretly
switched their planet
with Folgers crystals.
- Omigow, you take the lead.
Go on.
- [Joel] This planet is a
cookie, a crunchy cookie.
- Yeah, yeah.
Queen to queen's pawn 4.
- [Joel] We know.
- I'm right behind you.
- I don't understand.
I'm puzzled by these
strange flashes
of light which we keep seeing.
- [Joel] I'm also
bemused and charmed
by this plucky planet.
- Is bursting all around us.
What do you make
of them, Orloff?
- [Servo] Flavor buds.
- In my opinion, the atmosphere
in this area is ionized.
- Well, what's the cause?
- Atomic radiation.
- Then that means that
they're attacking us
and Brinkmann.
- We must fly lower.
We must get below
this bank of clouds
if we want to establish
contact with Brinkmann.
- And you should
all call each other
before the next costume party.
- Brinkmann calling
Cosmostraiter.
Please answer me, over.
- [Joel] This isn't
funny anymore, sirs.
(alarm blaring)
- Omigow.
- I'm bolting.
This is bogus.
- [Robot] Listening.
Be careful.
Danger.
- [Servo] Oh poison
gas for atmosphere?
Give me more of that.
- [Robot] Intense radiation.
Eight (mumbles).
- How long can we stay here?
- About three minutes ago.
- [Robot] Eight minutes maximum.
- Turn back, Omigow.
- [Joel] bidi, bidi.
Thanks for the promotion, jerk.
- Cosmostraiter, Cosmostraiter.
I don't hear you.
- Come on guys, stop it.
Stop mocking me.
- Hello, hello?
Do you hear me?
This blasted radioactive forest
won't let radio waves through.
Go on, Omigow, go on.
- [Joel] bidi bidi
bidi, beat cheeks.
- Keep on.
- Keep going, that's it.
Keep going.
(explosion)
(all shouting)
(dramatic music)
- Hold it, Omigow.
They're attacking us.
- It turns out he was
flying a Pinto-copter.
- Do you hear me?
The crawl-o-copter's exploded.
- A flash.
- [Servo] Oh I think that was
probably Bob cashing it in.
- What was it?
- I don't know.
Computer shows a pressure wave.
Apparently an explosion.
Distance, 120 miles.
- Brinkmann.
- Or it could be a signal
from the Venusians.
- [Joel] Or Bob's fiery death.
- We better land at
once, as best we can.
Talua, make a careful
check on our position
and try to contact Brinkmann.
- [Servo] Yeah, yeah.
When I get to it,
when I get to it.
(tense music)
- Omigow, back here, quickly.
- Hey, the carpet broke.
- [Joel] Oh boy, he's fallen
into a super ball test chamber.
Shopper always
leaves you laughing
ah-ha-ha-ha.
Yeah, it looks like
we got visitors, boys.
Come on, smart
boy, try your hand.
Come on.
Go ahead, I sit on the
right hand of the devil,
I am evil incarnate.
Go ahead.
Hey, I'm tougher than you.
- [Crow] Hey, I could get
about a buck for this.
I'm keeping it.
- [Servo] I wonder if
they're good eating.
You could boil them in beer.
- [Joel] Come back, we
have yet to taunt you.
We are the planet
of novelty items.
- Stand by.
- Deceleration rockets.
- Thrust, 18, 21.
24.
- 42, hut, hut.
Hike, go long.
- [Servo] It's Roger Ramjet
and his American eagles.
Take their proton pills.
- Hey hey, I'm down here.
(mock coughing)
Hey.
- [Joel] I'm glad you're back.
We make excellent
stocking stuffers.
You will come to
know that in time.
- [Servo] I know
how to cheer him up.
Tickle machine, tickle machine.
- Get him, get him.
(mock laughter)
Lock it.
Looks like a bad neighborhood.
- [Joel] Plaster doggy doo?
Rubber vomit?
What is this?
- Planet of Johnson Smith.
- [Servo] Hey, these prices
are quite reasonable.
- His crawl-o-copter exploded.
Poor old Brinkmann.
- There's the cause.
There's a high tension
line underground.
Durand, get the
crawlers out of the way
or the next time
the voltage mounts,
exactly the same thing
will happen to us.
- [Joel] Oh it just
looks like a big fish.
- Mommy, Daddy, I am home.
- [Joel] Oh, you
wonderful, fun-derful
spunky little robot.
(mock kissing noise)
- Omigow.
- [Servo] Oh my god?
Did he say oh my god?
- Brinkmann, we
thought you were dead.
- [Joel] I am filled with life.
Get to know me, friends.
- Why, what do you mean?
- There's a high
tension line over there.
- [Servo] Oh, what do you know?
- Now, your machine blew up
just because you landed right
on top of that
surface power line.
- [Joel] Oh, that's rich.
- All we have to
do was to follow it
and it will probably leads us
to the inhabitants of Venus.
- Oh you kill me.
- Or not.
- There's no point
in trying to do that.
I've already found the
inhabitants of Venus
and I've brought one
of them back for you.
- [Servo] Yeah, they're on sale.
Really reasonable, too.
- What is it?
- [Joel] It's art.
You bring your
preconceptions to it.
- I wonder if it
is a form of life.
- Great, he put another
life form in his pocket.
- All right, T'Chen Yu.
- [Servo] Why are
you still here?
Beat it.
- Let's go and try
to follow that line.
- Okay.
- Still feel stupid?
(mock engine revving)
- Omigow, come on.
- [Servo] Kam-I-ken?
- [Joel] Yeah yeah, here I come.
bidi bidi, beats all.
That's the way these
clowns order me around.
- Crawler, please come in.
Crawler, please come in.
- [Servo] Grab it.
- [Crow] Would you
like fries with that?
- There's something
very strange here.
A white sphere that looks
like an immense golf ball.
- [Servo] I think
he meant goofball.
- and it's teed up.
Looks like a Schlesinger Nine.
What a hell of a line.
- It's incredible.
You think it's a
machine, Orloff?
- Well, I can't say yet.
I don't know.
Everything here is so strange.
- [Joel] Why do they
have a bent coat hanger
around their mirror,
is that foreshadowing?
(laughing)
- Then, perhaps,
we'll understand.
- [Joel] You know, we've
become fast friends.
- Let me know when you've
got your instruments ready.
Now, I'll need all
the figures I can get.
- [Servo] Bugles, trombones.
- Good.
- I knew he'd say that.
- Talua, stay in
first contact with us.
- Very well, professor.
(tense music)
- I am looking at Venus
on the observation screen
at the Cosmostraiter.
Everything is strangely quiet.
Is this the calm
before the storm?
Why don't the Venusian's answer?
- [Servo] Why do I talk
into my toothbrush?
- Are these metallic
insects really the masters
of this planet?
- Ah, who cares?
- T'Chen Yu is
working day and night
to solve the mystery of
these strange creatures.
- Tonight, big sale at
Bill Fiber Oldstown.
We've got hot dogs for
the kids and suckers.
Speaking of suckers, look
at this sucker over here.
A 1928 porter.
Hey, come on down.
- [Joel] What a day, huh?
- [Servo] Hey, how are
the sea monkeys coming?
- [Joel] Hey, give me
a crack at that, huh?
Come on.
- We have investigated
your strange inhabitants.
They're completely harmless.
They're not a form of life.
- Well now think how
scared I was in that hole.
- Your discovery is more
significant than you think.
I put one of the
microcrystal in the marrocks.
Listen.
(ethereal electronic whirring)
- [Servo] Oh yeah, that's
really significant.
- Can't you get the
station in clearer?
Don't you have a convertor
box or some tin foil
to put on the antenna?
- [Servo] Rabbit
ears might do it.
- [Joel] Oh, that's sad.
- [Servo] So.
- Yes.
Those were the voices
of the Venusians.
I would say that these
strange metallic insects
had a way of storing
sound effects.
- [Joel] Groovy.
- Are you trying to tell us
that the Venusian's
used these insects
to record both speech and sound?
- That's right.
- But that's fantastic.
- [Servo] Thanks,
like you'd know.
- Well that would
mean that the hole
which Brinkmann fell into,
is a chamber of archives.
- [Crow] Oh right, and
they were all librarians.
- Of this planet.
- But then where could
the inhabitants be?
He certainly saw
a spaceship land.
He couldn't of missed it.
Yet, nothing happened.
- [Servo] Oh, maybe
there was a ball game on.
- Nothing at all.
- And my machine blowing up.
You call that nothing?
- [Servo] Yeah.
- I need more figures.
- We had figures.
Strange figures.
- More of those
metallic insects.
- [Servo] Forceps.
- [Narrator] The
research program
was going according to plan.
We are all fascinated
by the petrified forest.
- [Joel] And it likes us, too.
- [Narrator] Our
spacesuits are so heavy
that working outside
the ship is difficult.
The investigation
of the power lines
leading to the white sphere
and measurement
attention changes
is down by a silo craft.
The storms, which
whip across Venus,
only make the work harder.
- You know, these winds
- That's where the lines
lead to, all right.
There's no doubt.
- [Servo] Yeah, I know.
I was a meter man, once.
- That's it.
- [Servo] Yup.
That's the ticket.
- [Narrator] T'Chen was
collecting samples of the sand
carried by the storm.
- [Joel] At least, he
thought it was sand.
- [Narrator] Sometimes
they are radioactive
sometimes they are not.
- [Servo] Sometimes they
are soft and squishy.
- [Narrator] For traces of life.
The long Venusian night
is always proceeded
by a violent storm.
- [Servo] That's the
Santa Ana coming in.
- Tee time, star date
52-39 point five.
- [Narrator] Then the
outside work must stop
and we spend our time studying
what we have found so far.
- Then we go inside to
see what the carpenters
are doing with that
Italian quarry tile.
- Do you think this
petrified forest
is a biological formation?
- [Servo] I think you
oughta tighten the wingnut
down on that camera.
- It could come from
a dried up seabed.
- You're wrong.
- [Joel] This is
our secret fort.
We're gonna keep
T'chen Yu out, okay?
- Professor Sikarna has
been feeding figures
and data into the
electronic brain
and he now has some conclusions.
He says that the
petrified forest
is an enormous energy projector.
- Oh he does, does he?
Can you believe this guy?
Geeze.
- That it was built by
the inhabitants of Venus.
- Yes.
This petrified forest was made
to be a weapon of aggression.
- [Servo] Wish we had one of
them weapons of aggression.
- But then something
went unexpectedly wrong.
- Bush was elected.
- Perhaps they've
decided to disarm?
- [Joel] Oh you
think that's funny?
- I'm afraid it was
more serious than that.
The metal insects
you found for us
show something very significant.
- That's very interesting.
- [All] But stupid.
- Go on, tell us more,
Professor Sikarna.
- [Servo] Oh,
don't patronize me.
- I do not get the full effects
but I think that a terrible
catastrophe took place on Venus.
- [Servo] Yeah,
you guys arrived.
- It meets a certain stage
and I can't get any further.
It's chaotic.
Its like, it's like
everything was broken.
- [Joel] Someone get me
some juice or something.
- Now if there really
was a catastrophe.
It would change the face
of the whole planet.
Then it was so
huge a catastrophe
as to be absolutely beyond
our powers of comprehension.
- So you're saying
it was really big?
- We can only
solve this problem.
- [Servo] Duh.
- By means of further
systematic research.
Take this great white sphere
to which all these
power lines lead
and whose function
we don't understand.
- [All] Please.
- It appears to be a
giant transformer unit.
Or else it is, a
force field generator.
- You really have
no clue, do you?
- Another strange
thing is that there
is periodic tension in
the main power line.
- I, I feel it.
- I would even suggest
that there might
still be Venusians
inside the sphere.
- [Servo] Oh you
would, would you?
- A colossal catastrophe
that befell their planet.
They could still be trying
to send an SOS to
another station.
- What should we do?
- [Joel] I'm gonna fix my hair.
- We must go out and explore.
We'll follow the main power
line to the other end.
- Yes.
- Oh that, huh.
Hey, not that quickly.
- [Joel] It's a
planet of caviar.
- [Servo] It's super ball world.
(mock engines revving)
(upbeat music)
- Morphinic freeway and
super city sold separately.
- [Joel] GI Joe action car.
GI Joe sold separately.
- We have been driving for
nearly seven hours now.
We are following the energy line
and so far we haven't
found a trace of life.
- [Servo] Says you.
- This power line's
got to end somewhere.
- [Joel] What a dope.
(mock engine revving)
- Harringway, shall
we keep going?
- Yeah, why not.
- [Servo] Hey Joel,
what's a herring weigh?
- [Joel] About a pound.
(laughing)
- [Servo] That's twice.
- It looks like they're driving
through polyunsaturates.
- [Joel] It looks
the town of Bedrock.
- [Servo] Oh and still
the Folgers flavor
crystals, I think.
- [Joel] It's a place
right out of history.
- Hey, it's an
interstellar Stuckys.
- We are still going forward.
Keep on following
us and watch out.
- What's that?
- Hey, it's Trump Casino.
- I don't know, it's
not natural forms.
It must of been
buildings of some sort.
- [Servo] Oh, they look like
real comfortable buildings.
Oh get me a lease.
(dramatic music)
They look like big
frozen loogies.
(dramatic music)
- [Joel] Huh, hell from on high.
That's not supposed to happen.
- Hey, doesn't
Superman live here?
- [Joel] If he does,
he's got freezer burn.
- There must of been as
high a temperature here
as on the sun.
- [Servo] Or Universal
Studios back lot.
- And every living
thing was destroyed
by an incredible catastrophe.
- [Joel] It was humdinger
of a doozy, it was.
- Or not.
- [Servo] Oh come on,
why can't I have a line?
- What are you thinking, Sumiko?
- [Joel] The color red?
No.
- Awful damage.
- [Servo] She had to
stay on her lithium.
(mock engine revving)
- [Joel] Hey look, they got
outer space dance belts on.
- Come.
Power line goes in here.
This must be the entrance.
- [Servo] Oh what was your
first clue, butt head?
- Come on, Omigow.
We're going in.
- [Joel] Come on,
we got a job to do.
- Maybe I care a
little too much.
- [Joel] Bidi-bidi-bidi.
what's in it for meati?
(eerie ethereal music)
- [Servo] The entryway.
Oh, Alexander Calder was here.
- Look, Venus and the Earth...
- Joel, what are we seeing?
- [Joel] Its that model
from the beginning.
- [Servo] Someone with
a very different vision
made this movie, guys.
- Yeah, it's from a
book by Lewis Carrol.
- [Joel] Uh oh, it's a
giant baby's crib mobile.
Let's get out of here.
Well, at least we know
they like to disco.
- Over here, there's a shaft.
- [Servo] John Shaft?
- [Joel] That John
Shaft's one bad--
- [Both] Hey, shut your mouth.
- [Joel] I'm just
talking about Shaft.
- [Servo] It's buster
penny time pill down there.
- A huge control room.
- But who was servicing it?
- [Joel] Say.
- Since its apparent that
this whole installation
is still under tension.
- [Joel] Sexual tension.
(sniffing)
(tense music)
- Omigow.
- Oh my god?
Oh my god, he's
saying oh my god.
- [Servo] Oh, did somebody
really cut the magma down there.
- Strange, what could it be?
- Might be the
missing power source.
- [Crow] I don't think so.
- Look at those bubbles.
- [Joel] You look at 'em.
I'm bitter.
- Could be a kind
of organic life.
- [Servo] Oh really?
(dramatic music)
It bounced back out.
- Note to myself.
Don't throw rocks at magma.
- [Joel] Um, um, that was me.
I'm sorry, you may want
to start running now.
- [Servo] Oh a
planet you step on
and it starts to crumble.
Oh, I want to go.
- Nice matte job.
- Omigow, stop.
- [Servo] Hanukah?
- [Joel] I'm gonna
fight this thing.
Oh, this planets got a
saggy diaper that leaks.
- [Servo] Oh, I want to swim
in that oozy blue smoky stuff.
- Up the ramp, Sumiko, quick.
- [Joel] Hey, where's Steve
McQueen when you need him?
- Looks like the
maple wants them.
- [Joel] Bidi-bidi-bidi,
this is getting weird, Buck.
- Looks like they're up
a creek with a paddle.
- [Joel] That's true.
- Or a plunger.
- Giant washing machine.
- Come on.
Give them a break.
They just stepped on a rock.
(dramatic music)
- It's like a Karen
Finley fountain.
(screaming)
- Sumiko, I'm coming.
- [Crow] Oh, looks
like it had a hell
of a grip on her.
- [Joel] Well that's
what they say.
Melts in your mouth,
not on your planet.
The Mars bar.
- Oh.
- [Joel] I'm not
hungry anymore either
now that I think about it.
- Brown 25.
Building block of the future.
- [Servo] I'd say
Mrs. Butterworth
is gonna have a lot
of explaining to do.
- Good.
- [Joel] With a
name like Smuckers
you really get the feeling
for real preserves.
- You wipe your feet
before you come in
here, young man.
- [Servo] You know
what they need?
Some Kao-pectin.
- [Joel] Yeah.
- Now it's leaking baked beans.
- [Joel] Oh nobody told us
there'd be burnt newspaper
at the end of this road.
- [Servo] No.
You got a little over in...
- We'll find a way out.
- Ann Margret must be
around here somewhere.
- Don't shoot, don't shoot.
- [Servo] Ah, go ahead.
See, pays to experiment.
- [Joel] Hey, it's the
quicker picker upper.
It just goes...
- [Servo] Cleans up in a jiffy.
- Looks like someone
stands corrected
on that don't shoot line.
- What was that?
- [Joel] About a million
pounds of doodie,
is what it was.
- Where are the others?
I can't see them.
- Bidi-bidi-bidi.
- Spunky, come back.
Come back, Spunky.
- Well, that scene
was a load of crap.
- [Servo] Beware the
turd of Altair Seven.
- [Joel] Spotlight dance.
- I see what Durand meant now.
It's a model they
use to work out
their plans of
attack on the Earth.
- Good thing the Venusians
can never get far away
from the bathroom.
- It said they would
first subject the planet
to a highly intense
radiation bombardment.
Thanks to this device,
they calculated
how atomic beams
could be directed to our planet.
- I think you are quite right
and directly beneath us
is their operation headquarters.
- [Servo] Neat.
There it is.
- [Joel] Oh, there's
joy in kookville.
- [Servo] Speaking
of joy, let's blow.
- The magic toothbrush
wills save them.
Go, toughy, go.
(doors whirring)
- And we'll be right
back after this message.
Hi, Ed Herlihy here
hoping you're enjoying
tonight's Klack festival
theater presentation
of First Spaceship to Venus.
You know, holiday season
is the perfect time
to enjoy Klack's
industrial salad based
snacks and snippets
anytime of the day or year.
Start the morning with
a technicolor yawn
by serving up piles of
flabby Klack leather pancakes
dotted with dicey coco stunks.
Kids can't resist the texture
of Klack's creamy
clotted palm spread,
squeezed out on horsey biscuits
and don't forget the
Sir Cheddar snack a lots
and top them with Jimmy Hats
for a western roundup
and safe snacking.
And Moms, don't forget
to serve the claver club
platters of salamander
finger-wiches,
creamy crust puppies,
and hey, try a load
of taco minced meat
relish parfait served
up in a tulip glass
for that touch of elegance.
Uncle Bob's just out
of the institution.
Celebrate with skin mittens.
Brightened up with gamey
forest meat stuffing
and don't forget those
Polynesian cheese devils.
Then, pinch off some Klack
hanger crafted cobra coils
to compliment a
Bastille day buffet
and lube up those cooter cakes
with that incredibly
edible, spreadable phlegm.
Watch kitty's
galvanic skin response
shoot through the ceiling
by wrapping him in Klack wrap
and making her a
festive centerpiece.
At lunch time, light
your hand on fire
and plunge it into
the traditional gut
loaf whistle pie.
Just like grandpa used to do
before they took him away.
And finally, dress your
holiday table in style
with a gold roasted
mutant hell beast.
Stuffed with flesh
button dressing.
Made fresh with Klack saladoos,
cooter croutons, and
grandmother's earlobes.
Always the best.
Accent with creamy
crust puppies,
velvety chode balls,
and of course, a mug
of holiday swill.
Remember, if you're
incapable of showing emotion
but know how to cook,
Klack has a snack idea for you.
And we'll be right back
after these messages.
(upbeat music)
- [Crow] If you'd
like to make a call.
Please hang up and call again.
- [Both] If you'd
like to make a call,
please hang up and call again.
- Sikarna, the glass
forest is radiating energy.
Come quickly.
(dramatic music)
- That's just what
I was afraid of.
- [Servo] Oh why
didn't you tell us,
mister know it all?
- Look at that.
- [Joel] Oh, it makes me sick.
- The sphere's turned red.
- Maybe it's embarrassed.
- I am not surprised.
- [All] Shut up!
- No.
Now everything is clear.
- [Servo] Yeah, sure.
- The sphere creates an
artificial force field
which strengthens
the gravitation.
- [Joel] Strengthens it?
- Diminishes it.
At this very moment,
the power is emanating.
- [Servo] Menting, yeah.
- When the energy is inverted,
the field will reverse itself.
- [Servo] Reserved, huh huh.
- We'll be hurled into space.
- Well, that's interesting but
does it belong in the script?
- There's still time.
- [Servo] Yeah, yeah, yeah.
If you build it, he will come.
- Hello, Harringway,
come in, please.
- Joel, what's a herring weigh?
- [Joel] About a pound.
(laughing)
- Threes the charm.
- [Servo] This is
where I want to live.
The weather's so great.
(soft dramatic music)
- Geeze, I hope
this baby starts.
I think I left
the dome light on.
- [Joel] Just throw
that stuff anywhere.
I kinda live out of my car.
(mock engine revving)
Get into these metal cars.
We'll be safe from
the lightning here.
- [Servo] In the future,
they drive AMC Pacers.
- I'm getting car sick.
- [Joel] Okay, who knows a song?
Come on, let's have fun.
- [Servo] I know.
- Oh hey.
- They're shadows.
- Thrown on the wall
when they were hit
by an atomic explosion.
- [Servo] So they all look
like Tina Turner, I guess.
- Incredible.
- Those crummy vandals.
Can't leave anything alone.
- And now the only thing
that is left of them
is their shadows.
(mock snoring)
- [Servo] Oh, I thought you
were gonna say something else.
- Goodnight and may god bless.
- The maddocks is
picking up commands
from the underground
nerve center.
- [Joel] I knew that.
- Look at the key it's
using to decode them.
- Why it's, it's
incredible, Sikarna.
- [Servo] Thank you.
- E=MC2.
- [Joel] I stole that.
- That's Albert
Einstein's old formula.
- Yes but their
intergradation factor
is a curved closed upon its own.
- [Servo] Wow, pretty neat.
- Hey come here, you
gotta check this out.
Look at this.
- Take a look, it's interesting.
- [Joel] Well, that's first.
- [Servo] Oh, that's disgusting.
Neat, though.
- That's wonderful.
Those are seeds.
- I know, they're mine.
- They're plant seeds.
- Yeah.
- Where did you find them?
- I found them on the surface,
near the nerve center.
- [Servo] Spilled them.
- They were certainly
carried there
by one of those big storms
and if these seeds
are still fertile,
it proves there is
life on this planet.
- [Intercom] Professor Sikarna
wants everybody in
the maddocks, please.
- [Joel] Oh, that's just
great, we're busted.
- I knew you were
going to cut to me.
- Our researches on the metal
insects found in the cave
have told us so little
of this planet's history.
As to the message we heard,
there's no doubt about it.
- [Joel] They said.
- [All] Run!
- The inhabitants of
Venus were contemplating
launching an atomic
attack on our planet.
Now the attack
wasn't carried out.
- Good for us.
- An accident they didn't
expect upset their plan.
- The A-Team.
- Their atomic weapons
got out of their control.
- [Servo] As did their bowels.
- Chain reaction was unleashed
and they all perished.
- Only their shadows remained.
- [Joel] I knew that.
- Energy projectors,
although partially destroyed,
are capable of working again.
If their energy reactions
are set in motion by
some accident or
even by one of us.
- Why, what do you mean?
That we've started the reaction?
- No, baldy did.
- When that rock fell
into the black mud,
what happened?
- Oh the rock.
Would you let that die?
- As if the slime
was a living thing.
- Then something
terrible happened.
The slime began to grow rapidly.
- Then it got its own series.
- Dilated.
Now tell him.
What happened next.
The black slime started to move.
- Yes, it began to follow us.
We were cornered.
- What did you do?
- I used the (mumbles) ray gun
and I shot into it.
- [Servo] Then we frightened
it away with a coat hanger.
- You should never
have done that.
You started an atomic reaction.
- [Joel] Oh, everybody's
dumping on me.
- We had no other
way of getting out.
- Yes.
You started a chain reaction.
Over the whole
atomic installation.
- Happy?
- Now we're really
in a nice place.
- [Servo] Yeah, now it's
really gonna hit the fan.
- What can we do?
- What time was it?
- 17 hours, 10.
- I remember.
- I knew that.
- Yes.
Yes, it was at that moment
the sphere turned red.
- It looks as if mass
changed into energy
by process rather like
that of the atom bomb.
- [Servo] I've written
a poem about it.
- The people of this planet
knew how to reverse the process.
They changed mass into energy
but also they could change
energy back into mass.
- Fantastic.
- The inhabitants of
Venus are, or rather were,
far in advance of us in the
applications of physics.
That's one thing we
have to acknowledge.
- [Joel] Bidi-bidi-bidi.
I gotta go walkies.
Bidi.
- What the Sam scratch?
- [Joel] Hey, you kids,
stop running up there.
- Omigow, stop.
Omigow!
- I'm gonna get you, you,
your mother and I are very--
(mock groaning)
- [Servo] Bingo.
- [Joel] Bidi-bidi-bidi.
Taste my steel.
- Brinkmann, switch
off all the automats.
- Come and help me.
- Tweaky pops the clutch
and tells the dark
to eat his rust.
- The glass fires off.
- [Servo] What?
- The sphere is turning red.
- [Servo] Wouldn't yours?
- Orloff.
- [Joel] What you call me?
- The radiation from
the glass forest
has upset Omigow's
electronic brain.
The marrock's computers
gone out of action as well.
- Look!
- Oh yes, neat.
Now can I get back to work?
- If the radiation keeps
on increasing like this,
we won't have a chance.
- [Servo] Yay!
- Even the Cosmostraiter's
light shielding
won't be enough to protect us.
- Durand!
(mock groaning)
- I think he has
eternal injuries.
- [Joel] Eternal injuries?
Even in the afterlife?
- Start up the rockets.
We must take off at once,
before it's too late.
- I'm a little bit
mad at your robot.
- Won't work.
The gravity field's
increasing more and more.
The radiations
paralyzed everything.
Nothing is working.
- [Servo] Oh tell
us some good news.
- The whole is nothing but
an inert lump of metal.
- [Joel] He used to be cool.
- You rang?
- There's only one chance.
- [Servo] Your fly's open there.
- Let's try to do what
the Venusian's did.
Make the energy of
the glass forest
and the sphere change
back into mass once more.
- Wrong, but thanks for playing.
- When the mud attacked
you on the tower.
- [Joel] I'll be right out.
- And you decided
to use the ray gun
which changed the
mass into energy,
I think I saw
something was happening
in the Venusian nerve center.
I think I know how to
stop the reverse process.
- [Servo] But I'm
gonna need a big grant.
- Can I use the rocket plane?
- [Joel] And take it with you.
- You're forgetting
the gravity field.
It won't fly.
- [Servo] It's a crazy idea
but it just might work.
- Now get out of his way,
he's got a copter to fly.
- I'll come with you.
- [Joel] You won't
even know I'm there.
I'm just sit in the
corner and read.
- [Servo] Hey look,
Venusian blinds.
(laughing)
- Hey, it's Eric
Robert's sex table.
- [Servo] Okay, up there,
feet in the straps.
Oh, oh no, it's for him.
Oh, I see.
(tense music)
- [Joel] That planet is
covered with creamy nougat.
- They're entering
the Venusian city.
The hurricane is
getting much worse.
How is Harringway?
- About a pound.
Oh we did that.
I was just, I didn't.
Okay.
- Hit him.
(upbeat music)
Oh great, admit me into
this hospital right away.
This guys thinks
he's Issac Asimov.
- Hip bone connected
to the femur bone.
I don't remember.
(mock shouting)
At least you could
of put me under.
- [Joel] He's breathing
out of a football.
- How are you coming
along, Durand?
- [Joel] I think I
found my class ring.
- Can you, can you hear me?
Where are you?
- [Servo] Yeah, right
under the table.
- They're starting to climb down
into the Venusian nerve center.
(tense music)
- [Servo] Oh, come,
scrapped my knee.
Oh, oh.
Slack, slack, give
me some slack there.
- You know, any interest I had
for them getting
safely off the planet
has been completely erased
by a miasma boring,
technical stuff.
- [Servo] You said it.
- [Joel] Come on, you guys.
Just try to stay with it.
If you would like to leave
a number, please call back.
If you would like to leave...
(dramatic music)
- [Servo] Oh, ouch.
- [Joel] Hit by a phone
- [Servo] T'chen Yu,
I'm dangling here.
- [Joel] Oh, it's
only my shoulder.
I've got another one.
It's okay.
- My spacesuit.
It's punctured.
- [Servo] And it's rented.
- I'm coming to help you.
- [Servo] I'm on my way.
- You must save the others.
- [Joel] Okay.
- Harringway, I can't
hold out for long.
- [Servo] Hang way?
- My air's escaping.
- Hey, could you
give me some slack?
Oh, nevermind.
- The sphere is white again.
Look, Sikarna.
- Ready to pop.
- Has succeeded in
reversing the field.
My spacesuit is punctured.
My oxygen's escaping and the
safety device has failed.
- [Joel] Yeah,
yeah, shake it off.
You whiner.
- [Servo] Apparently
there's a list
of all people who
died in this film.
Oh, sign me up.
- I'll set off at once
in the rocket plane.
I'll get you out
of it, T'Chen Yu.
Hold on, I'm coming with oxygen.
- [Joel] And bells on.
- T'Chen Yu.
- Bless you.
- Gesundheit.
- Hello, T'Chen Yu.
- Bless you.
- Hold on.
Brinkmann is coming.
(tense music)
- Whee!
- T'Chen Yu.
- Bless you.
- I must talk to him.
T'Chen Yu, listen to me.
Those seeds that you
found, they're growing.
They're growing, T'Chen Yu.
- Tall and proud.
- You've proved that
there's life on the planet.
Yes, T'Chen Yu, there's
still life on Venus.
- [Servo] I'm dying
an agonizing death
and yet my seeds are growing.
I'm the happiest
boy on the planet.
- [Joel] If you
like to make a call,
please hang up and call again.
- [Servo] If you'd
like to make a...
(ethereal tense music)
- The breaking motors are off.
The braking motors.
- [Joel] Are off.
- Talua, T'Chen Yu, Brinkmann.
- [Servo] Quick.
- Come back at once.
- I knew they might die.
- We're being pushed
off the planet.
The reverse process
is in action.
The energy field is
acting like a catapult.
- The negative
gravity is increasing.
- [Servo] There, see?
Look.
♪ Happy birthday
- Oh, sure, they're all
gonna die but it looks cool.
- Brinkmann, can you hear me?
We're being hurled into space.
Talua, T'Chen Yu, Brinkmann.
Are you receiving me?
- [Radio] Sumiko.
Sumiko.
- Orloff, we must
try and go back.
Please.
- [Servo] Don't bother
me, I'm driving.
Get away.
- Hey guys, help me.
- Where are you?
- Help.
- Are you receiving me?
I can't get back.
I'm being held up (shouting).
- [Servo] Yeah, yeah, too bad.
- Rocketing off the charts
with that immortal hit,
it's Bob's death.
Next, coming up, Rocketman.
- [Joel] Boy, Estes has
nothing on those guys.
- My dear friends
would never leave me.
Hey!
Come back.
- [Servo] Wait a minute.
- Cosmostraiter?
You're taking off,
you're leaving me?
Harringway, Orloff,
don't leave me!
Don't leave me!
Cosmostraiter, Cosmostraiter.
- [Joel] At least he's
taking it like a man.
- You really find out
who your friends are.
- [Servo] Yeah.
(tense orchestral music)
Oh, well.
- Calling the Earth.
The Cosmostraiter is returning.
We have called them
but at the moment
there is no reply.
- There's an angry black
gentleman on line one.
- [Servo] They
could be out back.
(electronic beeping)
- [Joel] Would you please
just turn that off?
(groaning)
- [Servo] Attention mister
and missus North America
and all the ships at sea.
Gutless astronauts
left friends on planet,
returning today.
- Hey, she's nude.
(triumphant orchestral music)
♪ This is the triumph of
the end of the movie ♪
♪ They're coming back
♪ And we're here
to greet them. ♪
- Godzilla, God, oh
wrong movie, sorry.
♪ This is the music for the
landing of the rocket. ♪
- [Joel] The white
zone is for landing.
For all astronauts making
connecting flights,
please consult your flight.
- [All] A!
- [Servo] A, A, A, A.
It's the A-Team.
Sorry.
- Must be the varsity.
- [Joel] Hey, there's an M
car filled with A people.
MA.
- MA.
- [Joel] See, it's
a way to make words.
Ma.
- Neat.
(triumphant orchestral music)
Sounds like I got rhythm.
- I'm okay, I'm all right.
- [Joel] Hey, it's Devo.
- [Servo] A, A.
♪ This is the song
♪ That we sing
♪ When you come
home from Venus ♪
♪ It's really neat
♪ The dancing A guys
- Hey, maybe those guys
read Nathaniel Hawthorne.
- [Servo] Could be.
- We're more popular
than The Beatles.
- [Joel] Who are these people?
- [Servo] The tender love scene.
- I greet the Earth.
I greet you all.
- But not right now.
- [Servo] So what
were the guys like?
- We have learned much
but we have sacrificed a lot.
Too much.
(somber music)
- Mommy.
(sobbing)
- [Servo] Huh?
- What the.
- [Joel] Hey, she
looks kinda familiar.
It's my aunt Betty.
- [Servo] Joel, what's
she doing there?
- Let us honor the memory
of three great men.
- [Servo] They're
standing right here.
- Talua saved the
expedition from disaster.
- And then became compost.
- T'Chen Yu.
- Bless you.
- Discovered life on Venus.
And Brinkmann.
- [Joel] Screamed like a baby
when we flew off and left him.
- May they never be forgotten.
- [Servo] So, lunch everybody?
- We found traces of
a great civilization
that had advanced beyond
our comprehension.
The Venusian science
had gone beyond
their power to control it.
A dreadful catastrophe
fell upon them.
- My one piece of advice,
do not have the Venusian
poo poo platter.
- We still have a
great task before us.
- [Joel] Covering
the whole thing up.
- We must use our other planets.
We'll fly further and further.
It's mankind's destiny.
- [Servo] Oh.
Jump edit's important, too.
- Hey, who's this?
Who are you?
Hey, get off me.
Hey.
- [Servo] Let's go, guys.
- Better go.
(Servo cheering)
(doors whirring)
Oh man, at least
we're not gonna have
to go through that again.
- Oh, what a shame.
I'd like to go through some
of that again real soon.
- Actually, I kinda liked it.
- Oh, oh.
It was all too beautiful.
Like watching the old new
adventures of Perry Mason.
Or any Monte Markham
television project.
- Yeah, it kinda
remind me of like
mornings I'd eat way
too much sugar crisp
and then watch The Three Stooges
and you could kinda
smell moth balls
in the other room.
- Oh, that sounds
like cozy fun, Joel.
- Oh, it made me feel like I did
after I learned that Neil
Diamond wrote Red, Red Wine.
Oh, too giant scoops
of that for me.
- Well, I thought
it was pretty good.
I mean it had some spots
that were kind of slow
but I liked the
international flavor
and well, it had
a lot of action.
- Kinda reminds me
of watching Stallone
explain his theory of
life on the Donahue show
and you can taste copper.
- Oh, no, no, no.
If watching that
movie was like nodding
through the entire Jerry
Lewis Labor Day telethon
complete with a tearful Dean
Martin Jerry Lewis reunion.
Mr. Bojangles, and Joey Bishop.
And only waking up during
the parts of the show
that come from the lame-o
local network affiliates.
Sign me up for
hours of that kind
of rip our collect hearts out
and show 'em to us on
national television.
That's what I
wanted, more of it.
I don't think so.
- Hey.
- Wow, well.
I guess we should.
I guess we should read
a letter now, huh?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, well anyway.
Got some letters here from,
thanks for writing
in, everybody.
Really appreciate it.
This first one comes
from Amy Bochard
of Boys Ranch, Florida.
She writes, Dear Crow,
let's put that up on
still-store, there, Cambot.
Dear, Crow, Tom Servo,
Joel, and Gypsy.
You guys are real funny.
I want you guys to write back.
My whole family likes
to watch your movie.
We watch seven of your movies.
We like the beach
movie the best.
Amy Bochard, seven years old.
And there's a drawing
and it's got me saying,
Puma, Puma, Puma.
Or the guys saying,
Puma, Puma, Puma
and then it says
Lewis Moffitt, 1959.
Then its got Tom Servo saying,
Puma, Puma, Puma.
And I'm going, Meow, Meow, Meow,
and you're going,
whoo, whoo, whoo.
- Very cute.
- Yeah.
And then there's this one.
This is from Jennifer
Michelle Kayless from Lebanon.
Wow.
Put that on still-store there.
And that says, Dear
Crow, I like you.
- [Crow] Hey, I like you, too.
- Me and my Daddy die laughing.
Uh, question.
Okay.
Hey, I like that movie with
the girl singing a song
and you started dancing.
How are you so funny?
Question mark
talent.
Question mark.
- [Crow] Read the book.
- Yeah.
- Question mark.
- Anyway, Tom, you
want to read that uh...
- He's kind of out it.
- Do you want to read it, Crow?
- Oh, read the address
so that a bunch
of pathetic urchins
can write to us?
Sounds like super fun.
- Oh, come on.
- Just kidding, just kidding.
- Oh you little.
I'm gonna give
you a chin rascal,
you little dickens, yeah.
- I'm not dead.
I'm getting better.
- Hey, he's okay.
- I'm so happy, happy, happy.
- Oh good, he's all right.
Hey, chin rascal time, Servo.
(laughing)
Looks like we're a
family again, huh?
What do you think, sirs?
- Oh you guys are too much.
I'm gonna give
myself a chin rascal.
- Frank!
(heaving)
- Looks like I'm
gonna have to do this
all by my wittle self.
Ah, chin rascal, chin
rascal, chin rascal.
(heaving)
(soft upbeat music)
(all cheering)